{
    "id": "f92c3ea785de4d99bff23fa27c12ae7f",
    "title": "Or, Or Else, Otherwise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We must hurry up .................... we will be late for the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "otherwise",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c782c0666be34cee8612ca780095c8fe"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must reach home before 8 oâ€™clock ............................. my mother will get angry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "otherwise",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85dbf02844974f6cbc938feb771d75b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must work hard ....................... you will fail.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "otherwise",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfe91f4cfdb34c9b84b121770e44c292"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ought to put the meat in the oven now, ............................ dinner will not be ready when the guests arrive.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "or else",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94c31392d3274220a16d1aa7245b82e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Walk carefully .................... you will fall.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or else",
                "unless",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6c57dd3bf8524cb78e80042e9a227b20"
        },
        {
            "question": "Leave at once .......................... I will call the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or else",
                "unless",
                "until"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c75ced45c2c047d8abf8a9cc59bf4824"
        },
        {
            "question": "Consult a doctor immediately, ....................... your health will get worse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or else",
                "unless",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7353d08777ba4ce48759535dd4a98b2e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We must water the plants ........................., they will die.",
            "description": "Otherwise is not a conjunction. It is a transitive adverb. We use a semicolon before otherwise. ",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "otherwise",
                "or"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f5b5b915641e47989366059f9cc43091"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put the milk in the fridge ....................... it will turn sour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "otherwise",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f444e02ced024b78a9725d7842f7a5cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He should start exercising ............................, he will get fat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "otherwise",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3eff5e0fd62548ceb5c335da69483d7a"
        }
    ]
}